<?xml-stylesheet href="../../../../render/biglevel.xsl" type="text/xsl" ?>
<level>
  <type>Subchapter</type>
  <num>I</num>
  <heading>General Provisions</heading>
  <ns0:include xmlns:ns0="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" href="47-401.xml"/>
  <ns0:include xmlns:ns0="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" href="47-402.xml"/>
  <ns0:include xmlns:ns0="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" href="47-403.xml"/>
  <ns0:include xmlns:ns0="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" href="47-404.xml"/>
  <ns0:include xmlns:ns0="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" href="47-405.xml"/>
  <ns0:include xmlns:ns0="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" href="47-406.xml"/>
  <placeholder>
    <type>Repealed</type>
    <section>47-407</section>
    <heading>Powers of Mayor - Waiver of interest and penalties.</heading>
    <text>Repealed.</text>
    <level>
      <type>annotations</type>
      <level>
        <heading>History</heading>
        <text>(June 25, 1938, 52 Stat. 1201, ch. 702, § 7; enacted, Apr. 9, 1997, D.C. Law 11-254, § 2, 44 DCR 1575; June 9, 2001, D.C. Law 13-305, § 406(c), 48 DCR 334.)</text>
      </level>
      <level>
        <heading>Prior Codifications</heading>
        <text>1981 Ed., § 47-407.</text>
        <text>1973 Ed., § 47-307.</text>
      </level>
      <level>
        <heading>Legislative History of Law 13-305</heading>
        <text>For Law 13-305, see notes following § 47-405.</text>
      </level>
      <level>
        <heading>Editor's Notes</heading>
        <text>Section 410(d) of D.C. Law 13-305 provided: "Section 406(a), (c), (j), (m), (p), (q), (s), (w), (bb), (dd), (ee), (hh) through (kk), (mm) through (oo), (qq) through (uu), (yy), (zz), (bbb), (ddd), and (fff) shall apply for all tax years or taxable periods beginning after December 31, 2000."</text>
      </level>
    </level>
  </placeholder>
  <ns0:include xmlns:ns0="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" href="47-408.xml"/>
  <ns0:include xmlns:ns0="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" href="47-409.xml"/>
  <ns0:include xmlns:ns0="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" href="47-410.xml"/>
  <ns0:include xmlns:ns0="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" href="47-411.xml"/>
  <placeholder>
    <type>Repealed</type>
    <section>47-412</section>
    <heading>Applicability of personal property tax provisions.</heading>
    <text>Repealed.</text>
    <level>
      <type>annotations</type>
      <level>
        <heading>History</heading>
        <text>(May 18, 1954, 68 Stat. 119, ch. 218, title XVI, § 1601; enacted, Apr. 9, 1997, D.C. Law 11-254, § 2, 44 DCR 1575; June 9, 2001, D.C. Law 13-305, § 406(d), 48 DCR 334.)</text>
      </level>
      <level>
        <heading>Prior Codifications</heading>
        <text>1981 Ed., § 47-412.</text>
        <text>1973 Ed., § 47-312.</text>
      </level>
      <level>
        <heading>Legislative History of Law 13-305</heading>
        <text>For Law 13-305, see notes following § 47-405.</text>
      </level>
      <level>
        <heading>Editor's Notes</heading>
        <text>Section 410(e) of D.C. Law 13-305 provided: "Section 406(b), (d), (f), (l), (n), (o), (r), (v), (x)through (aa), (cc), (ff), (gg), (oo), (pp), (vv), (ww), (aaa), (ccc), (eee), and (ggg) shall apply as of January 1, 2001."</text>
      </level>
    </level>
  </placeholder>
  <ns0:include xmlns:ns0="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" href="47-412.01.xml"/>
  <placeholder>
    <type>Repealed</type>
    <section>47-413</section>
    <heading>Jeopardy assessment and collection.</heading>
    <text>Repealed.</text>
    <level>
      <type>annotations</type>
      <level>
        <heading>History</heading>
        <text>(May 18, 1954, 68 Stat. 120, ch. 218, title XVI, § 1602; enacted, Apr. 9, 1997, D.C. Law 11-254, § 2, 44 DCR 1575; June 9, 2001, D.C. Law 13-305, § 406(d), 48 DCR 334.)</text>
      </level>
      <level>
        <heading>Prior Codifications</heading>
        <text>1981 Ed., § 47-413.</text>
        <text>1973 Ed., § 47-313.</text>
      </level>
      <level>
        <heading>Legislative History of Law 13-305</heading>
        <text>For Law 13-305, see notes following § 47-405.</text>
      </level>
      <level>
        <heading>Editor's Notes</heading>
        <text>Board of Personal Tax Appraisers abolished: The Board of Personal Tax Appraisers was abolished by Organization Order No. 121, dated December 12, 1957. This Order continued the Finance Office, under the Department of General Administration, composed of the Office of the Finance Officer, Property Tax Division, Revenue Division, Treasury Division, Accounting Division, and Data Processing Division, and also established a Board of Equalization and Review. Organization Order No. 121 was revoked by Organization Order No. 3, dated December 13, 1967, Part IVC of which prescribed the functions of the Finance Office within the newly established Department of General Administration and also established a Board of Equalization and Review in the Finance Office, composed of the Finance Officer as Chairman, and 2 or more qualified persons who are conversant with real estate values in the District of Columbia, to be designated by the Finance Officer with the approval of the Director of General Administration. Under the provisions of the Order, the Board of Equalization and Review was empowered to review and equalize real estate assessments, hear complaints against real estate assessments and take appropriate action, and to transmit equalized assessments to the Commissioner for approval. Functions of the Finance Office as stated in Part IVC of Organization Order No. 3 were transferred to the Director of the Department of Finance and Revenue by Commissioner's Order No. 69-96, dated March 7, 1969. The latter Order also provided that the Director of the Department of Finance and Revenue serve on the Board of Equalization and Review (now the Board of Real Property Assessments and Appeals). Office of Assessor abolished: The Office of Assessor was abolished and the functions thereof transferred to the Board of Commissioners of the District of Columbia by Reorganization Plan No. 5 of 1952. All functions of the Office of the Assessor including the functions of all officers, employees and subordinate agencies were transferred to the Department of General Administration by Reorganization Order No. 3 of the Board of Commissioners, dated August 28, 1952. Reorganization Order No. 20, dated November 10, 1952, abolished the Office of the Assessor and transferred the functions to the Finance Office in the Department of General Administration. The same Order provided that an Office of the Assessor would be created in the Finance Office. Reorganization Order No. 20 was superseded and replaced by Organization Order No. 121, dated December 12, 1957, which provided that the Finance Office (consisting of the Office of the Finance Officers, Property Tax Division, Revenue Division, Treasury Division, Accounting Division, and Data Processing Division) shall continue under the direction and control of the Director of General Administration, and prescribed the functions thereof. The executive functions of the Board of Commissioners were transferred to the Commissioner of the District of Columbia by § 401 of Reorganization Plan No. 3 of 1967. Organization Order No. 121 was revoked by Organization Order No. 3, dated December 13, 1967, Part IVC of which prescribed the functions of the Finance Office within a newly established Department of General Administration. Functions of the Finance Office as stated in Part IVC of Organization Order No. 3 were transferred to the Director of the Department of Finance and Revenue by Commissioner's Order No. 69-96, dated March 7, 1969. Office of Collector of Taxes abolished: See Historical and Statutory Notes following § 47-401.</text>
        <text>Section 410(e) of D.C. Law 13-305 provided: "Section 406(b), (d), (f), (l), (n), (o), (r), (v), (x)through (aa), (cc), (ff), (gg), (ll), (pp), (vv), (ww), (aaa), (ccc), (eee), and (ggg) shall apply as of January 1, 2001."</text>
      </level>
    </level>
  </placeholder>
  <placeholder>
    <type>Repealed</type>
    <section>47-414</section>
    <heading>Abatement of taxes.</heading>
    <text>Repealed.</text>
    <level>
      <type>annotations</type>
      <level>
        <heading>History</heading>
        <text>(Sept. 30, 1966, 80 Stat. 858, Pub. L. 80-610, title IX, § 901; enacted, Apr. 9, 1997, D.C. Law 11-254, § 2, 44 DCR 1575; June 9, 2001, D.C. Law 13-305, § 406(d), 48 DCR 334.)</text>
      </level>
      <level>
        <heading>Prior Codifications</heading>
        <text>1981 Ed., § 47-414.</text>
        <text>1973 Ed., § 47-314.</text>
      </level>
      <level>
        <heading>Legislative History of Law 13-305</heading>
        <text>For Law 13-305, see notes following § 47-405.</text>
      </level>
      <level>
        <heading>Editor's Notes</heading>
        <text>Section 410(e) of D.C. Law 13-305 provided: "Section 406(b), (d), (f), (l), (n), (o), (r), (v), (x)through (aa), (cc), (ff), (gg), (ll), (pp), (vv), (ww), (aaa), (ccc), (eee), and (ggg) shall apply as of January 1, 2001."</text>
      </level>
    </level>
  </placeholder>
  <ns0:include xmlns:ns0="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" href="47-415.xml"/>
</level>
